richdad.com 2004-06-23

# Privacy Policy

By viewing or using the richdad.com or related websites, you agree to the terms of the richdad.com Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. CASHFLOW Technologies reserves the right to change the Online Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Online Privacy Policy at the time of such use. However, we do not intend to change the fundamental tenet of this policy -- your information will not be sold to anyone outside of CASHFLOW Technologies, Inc. The information we collect is solely for the purpose of communicating with our customers and members of the CASHFLOW Community.

Collection of Personal Information   
When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering products, accessing media files, or entering contests, CASHFLOW Technologies may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is optional for you to provide your information and engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, CASHFLOW Technologies may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address and telephone numbers. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

**Security**   
Please note that any area of our site that requires you to reveal financially sensitive information (ie, your Credit Card number) to continue with an activity -- such as an online purchase -- is located on our Secure Server(s) and is backed by a Verisign Certificate. Verisign [ [http://www.verisign.com](http://www.verisign.com/) ] is recognized widely as the premiere security authority on the internet. 

**Other Eyeballs**  
Please note that any information you post to a public discussion forum or chat room, such as the CASHFLOW Technologies Discussion Forums, is available to all persons accessing that site. We have no way of preventing individuals or companies from contacting you if they've seen your information publicly posted.

**Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are delicious. Some sections of our site utilize cookies as a convenience for our visitors. As an example - whenever a visitor fills out an online form, we set a cookie, and if accepted, it will prevent the visitor from having to reenter their information for any other online form on the site. So if you provide your info on our Contact form, you will not be required to fill out the Online Video access form. However, you will be required to enter your information on our Order System as we need the most current information you can provide for order fulfillment. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. While CASHFLOW Technologies uses cookies to track your visit to RichDad.com, and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided CASHFLOW Technologies with personal information.

**Consistency**   
Please note that if you provide CASHFLOW Technologies with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that we may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that we may not), CASHFLOW Technologies cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored. Outside Sites, please note that CASHFLOW Technologies is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-CASHFLOW Technologies websites to which RichDad.com or any other CASHFLOW Technologies website may link.

If you have further questions, e-mail: [privacy@richdad.com ](mailto:privacy@richdad.com)

**Disclaimer**   
RichDad.com (CASHFLOW Technologies, Inc.) is designed to help readers obtain financial education and discuss ways to make investment and personal financial decisions for the purpose of becoming rich and shifting to the right side of the CASHFLOW Quadrant. The fundamental concept is that you should NOT rely solely upon the information or opinions you read. Rather, you should use what you read as a starting point for doing independent research on companies, opportunities, and investment techniques. Then judge for yourself the merits of the material that has been shared in our forum and at our site. 

The opinions and statements expressed by the community members on the discussion forum are not necessarily those of CASHFLOW Technologies, Inc. Also CASHFLOW Technologies, Inc. does not recommend or endorse any specific investments or business opportunities. We recommend that you research all investments and opportunities thoroughly as well as the team you will be joining. 

We are here to help you learn how to make investment and personal finance decisions for yourself in an effort to get out of the rat race. 

If you have further questions, e-mail: [privacy@richdad.com](mailto:privacy@richdad.com)
